Misael Souza de Paula

Mogi Mirim, São Paulo, Brazil



misa.gcp1@gmail.com



19 997971113



linkedin.com/in/misaelp

Summary

Ever since my first PC (with Windows 3.11 with MS-DOS), I was fascinated to understand how to have fun with my old computer. I still remember when I installed my first software through a floppy disk; When I began to use Linux OS distros to learn shell scripts and C, all the journey was plenty of happy discoveries and painful moments when nothing worked as imagined. Looking backward now, I know that those challenging moments help me to overcome any kind of trial to learn new technologies and still have fun through the process.

This passion carried me to work solving problems with coding and dynamic cloud infrastructure. Solving problems using technology constantly gives me the purpose to help my team and my employers achieve their goals.

Specialties: AWS Cloud Engineering and Architecting, Python, System integrations, DevOps, Kubernetes, Airflow, Machine Learning pipelines.

Academic: System Programming, Cloud Networks, Data Science, Digital Products

Experience



DevOps Cloud Engineer | Full Stack Developer | Data Science Enthusiast

Itaú Unibanco

Jun 2019 - Present (2 years 8 months +)

Working with a Data Broker platform to process, ingest and integrate all IT data with data lakes and internal monitoring systems.

Itaú

Sr. Network Support Analyst

Itaú Unibanco

Apr 2018 - Jun 2019 (1 year 3 months)



Network Support Analyst

Agility

Sep 2015 - Apr 2018 (2 years 8 months)

IBM

Network Support Specialist

IBM

Apr 2015 - Sep 2015 (6 months)



Field Technical Support

Hewlett-Packard

Oct 2014 - Apr 2015 (7 months)

Infrastructure Operations Technician

Ativa-TS - Hewlett-Packard Jun 2014 - Oct 2014 (5 months)

College Scholarship Member

Fatec Mogi Mirim - Arthur de Azevedo Jan 2013 - Dec 2013 (1 year)

- + English Mentoring
- + Calculus/Statistics

Education



🕋 University of Virginia

Digital Product Management, Specialization

Oct 2021 - Mar 2022

Learning and applying modern practices to developing Digital Products and Agile Teams focused on Customer Digital Experience.

🥮 Universidade Estadual de Campinas

Especialização em Redes de Computadores, Information Technology 2018 - 2018

Udacity

Nanodegree Data Scientist, Artificial Intelligence 2019 - 2019

Fatec "Arthur de Azevedo" Mogi Mirim

Technology's Degree, Information Technology Project Management 2012 - 2015

Licenses & Certifications



CCNA Data Center - Cisco

Issued Jun 2015 - Expires Jun 2018 CSCO12740752

CCNA Routing and Switching - Cisco

Issued Mar 2015 - Expires Mar 2018 CSCO12740752



Issued Jan 2015 - Expires Jan 2018 CSCO12740752

(Application Delivery Fundamentals - F5

Issued Apr 2016 - Expires Apr 2018 F50000115300

TMOS Administration - F5

Issued Sep 2016 - Expires Sep 2018 F50000115300

LTM Specialist: Architect, Setup, and Deploy - F5

Issued Sep 2017 - Expires Sep 2019 F50000115300

TTM Specialist: Maintain and Troubleshoot - F5

Issued Jan 2018 - Expires Jan 2020 F50000115300

AWS Certified Developer - Associate - Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Issued Jan 2021 - Expires Jan 2024 SY6RVQFLBJEE15WG

Machine Learning Pipelines on AWS - Amazon Web Services (AWS)

AWS Certified DevOps Engineer – Professional - Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Issued Oct 2021 - Expires Oct 2024 BLM35XSDG2F4QD3Z

Skills

English • Team Leadership • Team-oriented • Software Development • Linux • Python • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • DevOps